Hanslowe, Kurt, Papers /4064
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Misc. publications, correspondence, xerox copies of articles, etc (Box 8)
  - Misc. Letters, News Clippings, Law Reviews, Views and Reviews, and Announcements, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Misc. Handwritten Notes (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Publications, term papers, misc (Box 9)
  - New York State Law Revision Commission: Draft of Administrative Procedure Act, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Judicial Review of Rules and Adjudications of Administrative Agencies by Professor Samuel M. Hesson File No. 1286 Docket No. 2286 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - S. 1663 A Bill to Amend the Administrative Procedure Act (1963) and Comments of Marvin Frankel and Walter Gellhorn, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Amendments to the Federal Administrative Procedure Act in S. 1663 (As Introduced) and in S. 1663 (Subcommittee Revision), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Uniform Law Commissioners' Revised Model State Administrative Procedure Act (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Record of States with Administrative Procedure Legislation and their Laws, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Model State Administrative Procedure Act (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: New York State Labor Relations Board and the Workmen's Compensation Board (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: Department of Labor Board of Standards and Appeals, Division of Employment, and Minimum Wage Board (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: Department of Labor Division of Labor Standards, Division of Labor and Management Practices, Bureau of Public Work, Division of Industrial Hygiene (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: Department of Labor Division of Industrial Safety Service, Bureaus of Factories and Mercantile Establishments, Construction, and Boilers, Building Plans Engineering Unit (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: Executive Department New York State Liquor Authority and State Commission for Human Rights (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: Executive Department Division of Parole, Board of Parole, Offices of General Services, and Bureau of Surplus Real Property (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: Department of State Athletic Commission, New York State acing Commission, State Harness Racing Commission, State Bingo Control Commission (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: Department of State Division of Cemeteries, Division of Upholstery and Bedding, Election and Law Bureau Division of Corporations, Bureau of Miscellaneous Records (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: Public Service Commission and Insurance Department (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: New York State Department of Health and Department of Motor Vehicles (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: Department of Agriculture and Markets, Department of Conservation (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Law Revision Commission Study of Administrative Procedures: Welfare Department, Reimbursement Division, Department of Civil Service (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Study of Administrative Procedures, Wisconsin Administrative Procedure Act Ch. 227 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Federal Administrative Procedure Act Co. 19 and Proposed Code of Federal Administrative Procedure H.R. 9926, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - New York State Law Revision Commission Report and Recommendations Relating o an Administrative Procedure Act, an Administrative Rule Making Procedure Act, and a Division of State Administrative Procedure Law, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Stenographic Transcript of Hearing on Draft of a State Administrative Procedure Act, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Stenographic Transcript of Hearing on Draft of a State Administrative Procedure Act, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Stenographic Report of Conference of Consultants on Administrative Procedure Study, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Reports by Oswald Vischi and M. Harold Dwyer to the New York State Bar Association Committee to Cooperate with the Law Revision Commission, and Committee Memorandum, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - NULL (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Second Preliminary Report Draft to the Legislature Relating to Study of Advisability of Legislation Providing Standards for Administrative Procedure and Misc. Papers (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Term Papers, exams, library reserve materials, articles (Box 10)
  - ILR 681 Exam May 21st Test Book #3-20, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - ILR 681 Exam May 21st Test Books #21- 44, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - ILR 681 Exam May 21st Test Books #45- 64 and Ellen Cord, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - US Supreme Court and Appeals Circuit Cases and Opinions, 1895-1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - US Supreme Court and Appeals Circuit Cases and Decisions, 1889-1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Report of Committee on Law and Legislation, January, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - S. 2810 A Bill Amending the NLRA with Respect to Emergency Labor Disputes, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Corporate Arbitration Awards and Findings, 1943-1949 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - ILR 681 Papers, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Papers, Assignments, Memoranda, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Labor Law Notes p.714 to End and Cornell Law Forum, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - ILR 681 Final and Midterm Examinations, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Intercollegiate Bibliography: Abstracts of Cases from Intercollegiate Case Workshops 1970, 1971, 1972, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - A Comparison of Two Possible Statutory Schemes for Agricultural Labor Law: The New California Statute and the NLRA- Betsy Harding, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - ILR 682 Class Assignments and Notes, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - ILR 682 Class List, Notes, and Term Paper Assignment, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Catherwood Library Acquisitions List, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Collective Bargaining in the State University of New York: A Thesis by Garry M. Whalen, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Restraints on Player Bargaining and Mobility in Professional Sports (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Bulletin and Letters, Map of Chautauqua County, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations Review, Harvard Law School Bulletin, Collegiate News and Views, and Cornell University Announcements, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - The Public Review Board, UAW Cases 366, 381, 406, 409, 411, 414, 415, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - American Arbitration Association Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Sources of Information in Public Sector Labor Relations: A Practitioner's Guide (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - ILR 682 Papers and Critiques, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Misc. Memoranda, Letters and meeting Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Law Review Recent Developments in Arbitration and Labor Law by F. Kevin Loughran, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - ILR 682's Response to Problem #2 Regarding NYS Department of Metal Hygiene and Civil Service Employees Association and Sid Moller's Award in Jones vs. Baltimore Transit Authority, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Arbitration between Civil Service Employee Association and NYS Department of Mental Hygiene and Department of Correctional Services, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - American Arbitration Association Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Misc. Letters, Newsletters and Promotions, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Memoranda, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Annual Faculty Report ('76- '77) and Special Faculty Meeting (May 27, '76), 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - 1975 Fall Term Reports (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - NYSSILR Course Descriptions and Check Lists for M.S. and MILR Candidates, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - ILR 682 Papers: Bishop- Seligson, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - IL 682 Papers: Shenker- Watkins and Waddell, Swedo, Shenker Joint Paper on Antitrust Decisions and the Connell Case, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Handwritten Notes and Doodles (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - US Supreme Court Pittsburgh Press Co. vs. Pittsburgh Commission on Human Relations, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - US Supreme Court NLRB vs. Granite State Joint Board, Textile Workers Local 1029, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Daily Labor Reports: Supreme Court Decisions, 1965-1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Supplement to Cases and Materials on Labor Law: Collective Bargaining in a Free Society by Oberer and Hanslowe, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Controversial Labor Cases Pending before the Supreme Court: Outline of Remarks by Hanslowe, "How to Prepare Grievance Arbitration Cases," and "A Woman's Point of View", 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - ILR 701 Possible Paper Topics, Law 575 Schedule of Pape Presentation, and Analysis of Multiple Year Teacher Contracts for School Year 1975-1976, 1974- 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - ILR 681 Midterm Spring 1974 and Final Exam Spring 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Notes (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - ILR 684: Employment Discrimination and the Law Syllabus, Professor Arthur B. Smith Jr., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action in Practice: A Preliminary Report to the Ford Foundation, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Opening Remarks a Developments in Law- Related Education Hearing by Senator John V. Tunney, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Misc. Pamphlets, Articles, and Wall Street Journal Clipping, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Notes (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Industrial Versus Craft Unionism, A Book Compiled by Julia E. Johnson, The H.W. Wilson Company, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Group Legal Services: A Summary Paper (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Hearings before the New York State Bar Association Committee on Professional Ethics Regarding Amendments to the Code of Professional Responsibility Relating to Group Legal Services, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - News Clipping and Statement by Murray H. Finley, Vice President and Manager of Chicago Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - New York State Employment Relations Board "Harold Newman's Cloudy Crystal Ball" and Journal of the Experimental Analysis of Behavior- "Animal Psychophysics: Improvements in the Tracking Method"- Harrison and Turnock, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - The Georgetown Law Journal vol. 63, No.4 March 1975 and "Economics, Politics, and the Law: The NLB's Division of Economic Research 1935-1940" by James Gross in the Cornell Law Review- 1970, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Stuart S. Nagel: "Off-The-Bench Judicial Attitudes" (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Susan T. Mackenzie Travel Request and Statistics Report, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Law School 1975-1976 Term Course Lists and Checklist for M.S. Candidates (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Daily Labor Reports and the Banjo Newsletter, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - US Supreme Court: Samuel L. Woods vs. North American Rockwell Corporation, United Transportation Union vs. The State Bar of Michigan, United Mine Workers of America vs. Illinois State Bar Association, 1967-1972 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Notes (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - ILR 684 and 701 Syllabi for Professor Arthur B. Smith Jr., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Case Decisions: Watkins vs. Steelworkers, Local 2369 and Cleveland Board of Education vs. LaFluer, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Susan Mackenzie Voluntary Labor Arbitration Awards (Class Assignment?), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - "Cases and Materials on Employment Discrimination Law" by Arthur B. Smith Jr., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - "Cases and Materials on Employment Discrimination Law" by Arthur B. Smith Jr., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - "Cases and Materials on Employment Discrimination Law" by Arthur B. Smith Jr., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Guidelines on Discrimination Because of Sex (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Employee Testing and Selection Procedures and Equal Employment Opportunity Guidelines (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Daily Labor Reports: Discrimination- Rules and Guidelines, 1971-1975 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - "A Theory of Fair Employment Laws" by Owen M. Fiss (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Fair Employment Practices Legislation and Cases/Decisions, 1963-1975 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Cornell Law Library Guide 1974-1975 and New York Magazine and Misc. Papers/Letters (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - US Court of Appeals Communication Workers of America vs. American Telephone and Telegraph Company, Goldfarb vs. Virginia State Bar and H.R. 7824 of 93rd Congress, An Act to Amend the Economic Opportunity Act of 1964 (1974), 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Unauthorized Practice and Advertising by Professor Martin, Miriam Brown (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - "The Office: A Facility Based on Change" by Robert Propst, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - (75-76) Student Payment Application and TAP Award, Code of Legislation of the Graduate Faculty (1968), Guide to Graduate Study (1975), 1968-1976 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Inmate Grievance Procedures and Arbitration in Prisons (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - New York State Employment Relations Board News, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Supplement to Cases and Materials on Employment Discrimination Law (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - USA vs. Steel Companies, Memorandum, and Rulings on Inquiries Regarding Equal Employment Opportunity Laws, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - "Executives and the Mid-Life Crisis", "The 'Meeting' Following Fact Finding in School District Impasses," and Report of Senate Judiciary Subcommittee on Separation of Powers, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - Staff Reports of the Subcommittee on Antitrust and Monopoly of the Committee on the Judiciary, US Senate Pursuant to S. Res. 61, 84th Congress 1st Session, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Labor Law Journal, A Commerce Clearing House Publication May 1954, and Michigan State Bar Journal Vol.36 No.1 (1957), 1954-1957 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Union Monopoly vs. The Public Interest, An Address by Ernest R. Breech, Labor Relations Reporter, National Association of Manufactures Letter and Public Relations Department Analysis on Du Pont- General Motors Suit, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Labor Education: A Study Report on Needs, Programs, and Approaches by Joseph Mire, "Films for Labor" by the AFL-CIO, and "Quotations by the Great Men of the Ages on the Most Significant Questions from the Beginning of History until Now", 1956 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - State and Federal Labor Legislation, US Department of Labor, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - labor Law Group Trust: Letters and News Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Committee on the Judiciary: Amendments to the Administrative Procedure Act, Comparative Print, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Industrial Relations Research Association: Letters, Meetings, Reports, Publications, 1958-1962 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Kohler Strike and Boycott, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - "Architects of Order"- The Ford Foundation, "Unions and Union Leaders of their Own Choosing"- The Fund for the Republic, "Labor Looks at the White Collar Worker"- Industrial Union Department, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - "The Foreign Competition Hoax"- he United Steelworkers of America (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - S.748 86th Congress 1st Session "Labor- Management Practices Act of 1959" (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - S.1555 "Kennedy Bill" 86th Congress 1st Session and Senate Report 187 Accompanying S.1555, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 4473 86th Congress 1st Session "Labor Bill of Rights Act of 1959" (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Mr. Kennedy's S.505, Mr. Elliott's H.R.8342, and Mr. Landrum's H.R.8400 86th Congress 1st Session, "Labor- Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959" (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Amendments to the Labor- Management Relations Act of 1947 and National Labor Relations Act 86th Congress 1st Session, Mr. Curtis' S.76, Mr. McClellan's S.1384, 1386, 1387, Mr. Barden's H.R.4474, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Mr. McClellan's S.1137 86th Congress 1st Session, "Labor- Management Basic Rights, Ethical Standards and Disclosure Act of 1959" (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Mr. Mundt's S.1002 To Establish Standards Protecting the Rights of members of Labor Organizations, Mr. Mundt's S.1311 To Require the Bonding of Certain Labor Union Officials, Mr. McClellan's S.1385 Prohibiting the Inclusion of Hot Cargo Provisions in Coll, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - John S. Forsythe Letter to Professor Vernon F. Jensen, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Kurt Hanslowe vs. Herbert Northrup (Joke?) and Federal Power Commission vs. Hope Natural Gas Company (Supreme Court 1944) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - New York Times Clipping and Labor Relations Reporters on Labor- Management Reform Acts, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959: Notes, Bill, Pamphlets, Reports, Quizzes (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Hanslowe Correspondence 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Hanslowe Correspondence and Misc. Pamphlets, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - State Bar of Michigan Labor Relations Law Section, Reports, Outlines, Addresses, Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Data on Santo (Sam) Perrone, alias Perroni, Pirrone re Perrone-Renda Briggs Deal and Beatings; Reuther Brothers, etc. (Box 13)
  - "Labor's Witness" A UAW Publication and Memoranda, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - "The Legal Enforceability of Collecting Agreements in the United States and Britain: Status and Consequences" by David Lowy and Anthony Bartlet, Civil Service Employees Association vs. New York State Department of Correctional Services, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Lieut. Joseph Sheridan Confidential Reports: Reuthers' Shooting, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Lieut. Joseph Sheridan Confidential Report: Reuthers' Shooting, 1953-1955 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Data on Santo (Sam) Perrone, alias Perroni, Pirrone and Background of Shooting P.1- 165 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Data on Santo Perrone Re: Perrone- Renda Biggs Deal and Beatings P.166- 362 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Data on Santo Perrone Re: Grand Jury Probe of Beatings- euther Bothers Shot P.363- 489 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Data on Santo Perrone Re: Grand Jury Probe of Beatings- Reuther Bros. Shot P.490- 565 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Volume Four Part I Re: The Dynamiting of UAW Headquarters, Etc. p.566- 620 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Volume Four Part II Re: The Perrone Et Al Stove Works Conspiracy Cases p.621- 744 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Volume Four Part III Re: Continuing Perrone Et Al Stove Works Conspiracy Cases and Subsequent Events p.745 to End of Report (895) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Short Reports and Correspondences, 1945-1957 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Confidential Reports and List of Toll Calls made from Hotel Astor by Melis, Tony Tocco, and Sam Perrone Among Others Around the Wedding of Salvatore Meli and Dolores Livorsi, 1952-1958 (Box 13, Folder 14)